{"question":"52 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"381 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"153 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"155 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"76 : 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"258 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"356 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"60", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"567 : 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"559 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"401 : 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"190 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"10 : 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"46 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"1 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"688 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"281 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"487 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"67", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"56 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"169 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"97 : 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"252 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"37", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"363 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"401 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"153 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"5 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"115 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"228 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"587 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"624 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"716 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"22 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"72 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"48 : 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"73 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"9 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"427 : 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"5 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"18 : 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"708 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"60", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"162 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"71 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"416 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"132 : 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"361 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"40 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"206 : 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"97 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"241 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"8 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"46 : 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"103 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"67 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"307 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"234 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"477 : 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"108 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"125 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"137 : 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"302 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"127 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"136 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"302 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"54", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"306 : 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"66", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"34 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"107 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"32 : 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"116 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"479 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"220 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"66", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"360 : 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"313 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"312 : 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"45 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"480 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"66", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"194 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"155 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"653 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"657 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"155 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"29", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"167 : 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"113 : 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"188 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"398 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"338 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"272 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"44", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"304 : 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"23 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"371 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"63", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"136 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"53 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"178 : 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"593 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"65", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"35 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"2 : 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"37 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"37", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"313 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"83 : 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"61 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"61", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"180 : 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"238 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"119 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"17 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"49 : 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"32 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"10 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"59 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"458 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"142 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"12 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"238 : 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"28 : 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"150 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"748 : 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"257 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"427 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"274 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"491 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"134 : 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"232 : 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"177 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"540 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"36", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"556 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"49 : 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"43 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"431 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"170 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"563 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"331 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"338 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"8 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"289 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"12 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"657 : 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"57", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"24 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"43 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"295 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"67", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"564 : 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"176 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"45 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"113 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"7 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"473 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"104 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"44", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"342 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"115 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"117 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"12 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"406 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"390 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"27 : 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"203 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"48 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"13 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"384 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"42", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"226 : 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"244 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"240 : 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"166 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"18 : 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"146 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"155 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"277 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"67", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"51 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"359 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"59", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"415 : 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"359 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"63", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"436 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"326 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"159 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"190 : 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"156 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"52 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"373 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"125 : 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"281 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"17 : 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"14 : 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"207 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"72 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"473 : 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"341 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"87 : 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"81 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"695 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"209 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"124 : 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"148 : 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"675 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"10 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"312 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"139 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"14 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"113 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"197 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"150 : 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"110 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"502 : 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"18 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"276 : 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"52 : 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"31 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"568 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"557 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"44", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"193 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"607 : 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"160 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"103 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"302 : 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"37", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"11 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"361 : 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"243 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"12 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"54 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"54", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"427 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"235 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"529 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"640 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"480 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"54", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"56 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"149 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"177 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"329 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"112 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"2 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"246 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"610 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"92 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"662 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"70", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"13 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"169 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"235 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"383 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"43 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"354 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"271 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"571 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"228 : 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"53 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"603 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"378 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"348 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"390 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"558 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"61", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"39 : 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"51 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"149 : 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"18 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"234 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"42", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"438 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"451 : 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"668 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"29", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"525 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"258 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"301 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"131 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"325 : 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"771 : 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"69", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"1 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"103 : 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"305 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"291 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"368 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"317 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"140 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"472 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"615 : 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"2 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"415 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"72 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"35 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"12 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"584 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"44", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"9 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"36 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"9 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"270 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"320 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"191 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"354 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"108 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"476 : 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"280 : 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"143 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"461 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"537 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"381 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"571 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"52 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"175 : 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"22 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"330 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"29", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"75 : 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"75", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"31 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"528 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"494 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"394 : 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"118 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"57", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"149 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"298 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"50 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"87 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"225 : 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"174 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"224 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"110 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"582 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"399 : 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"59", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"298 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"351 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"24 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"465 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"353 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"46 : 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"116 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"450 : 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"60", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"267 : 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"32 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"54 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"552 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"56", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"456 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"7 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"43 : 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"244 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"187 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"146 : 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"203 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"450 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"571 : 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"244 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"168 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"467 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"121 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"245 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"115 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"37 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"233 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"99 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"166 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"580 : 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"64 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"12 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"46 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"224 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"351 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"595 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"252 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"15 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"342 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"54", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"389 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"674 : 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"62", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"316 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"297 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"8 : 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"190 : 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"88 : 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"207 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"36", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"285 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"33 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"185 : 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"399 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"138 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"62", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"55 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"146 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"15 : 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"535 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"190 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"149 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"187 : 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"11 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"517 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"263 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"599 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"458 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"73", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"291 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"397 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"131 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"18 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"49 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"330 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"35 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"103 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"63 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"5 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"58 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"113 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"256 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"316 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"36", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"232 : 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"51 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"42 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"65 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"1 : 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"231 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"530 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"61", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"178 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"32 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"577 : 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"216 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"559 : 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"37", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"61 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"33 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"33", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"271 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"4 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"94 : 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"3 : 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"318 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"231 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"285 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"31 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"98 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"328 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"426 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"378 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"42", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"6 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"84 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"425 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"234 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"198 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"462 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"436 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"66", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"32 : 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"66 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"206 : 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"114 : 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"113 : 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"432 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"127 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"385 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"81 : 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"362 : 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"239 : 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"96 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"38 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"368 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"207 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"53", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"338 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"53", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"2 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"349 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"295 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"346 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"35 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"3 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"69 : 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"348 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"12 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"45 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"599 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"376 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"434 : 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"201 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"319 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"105 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"297 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"33", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"319 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"26 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"82 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"195 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"382 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"74 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"95 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"332 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"298 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"545 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"14 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"126 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"125 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"100 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"12 : 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"192 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"60", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"156 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"181 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"331 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"162 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"152 : 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"32 : 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"421 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"42 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"42", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"5 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"289 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"462 : 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"72", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"176 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"365 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"37", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"755 : 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"222 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"390 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"662 : 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"139 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"466 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"14 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"156 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"63 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"63", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"204 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"88 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"22 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"572 : 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"60", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"119 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"28 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"236 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"53", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"11 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"608 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"198 : 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"146 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"6 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"264 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"365 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"176 : 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"281 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"289 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"382 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"372 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"36", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"477 : 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"203 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"24 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"748 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"142 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"204 : 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"173 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"408 : 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"88 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"70 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"421 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"616 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"373 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"96 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"375 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"79 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"47 : 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"33 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"153 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"238 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"578 : 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"286 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"366 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"36", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"219 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"202 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"435 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"633 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"65", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"142 : 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"83 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"16 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"353 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"134 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"628 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"291 : 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"451 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"34 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"22 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"115 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"422 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"24 : 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"337 : 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"209 : 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"148 : 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"55 : 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"94 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"24 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"81 : 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"27 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"58 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"223 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"178 : 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"401 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"44", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"393 : 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"73 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"103 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"35 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"16 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"26 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"43 : 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"212 : 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"133 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"295 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"470 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"314 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"203 : 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"234 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"397 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"33", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"48 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"284 : 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"129 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"50 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"303 : 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"231 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"59 : 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"271 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"463 : 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"610 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"346 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"460 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"67 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"154 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"134 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"90 : 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"310 : 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"109 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"255 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"322 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"114 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"186 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"207 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"80 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"297 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"172 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"265 : 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"39 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"298 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"30 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"4 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"577 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"503 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"283 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"37", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"411 : 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"33", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"54 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"54", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"316 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"56", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"287 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"42", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"115 : 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"375 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"147 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"77 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"313 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"570 : 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"146 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"293 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"39 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"467 : 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"44", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"91 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"17 : 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"227 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"165 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"415 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"308 : 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"157 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"116 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"208 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"400 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"55 : 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"42 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"42", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"80 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"484 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"153 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"214 : 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"249 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"338 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"53", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"448 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"226 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"130 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"6 : 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"233 : 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"33", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"214 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"591 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"233 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"61 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"18 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"28 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"240 : 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"14 : 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"7 : 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"585 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"53", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"345 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"604 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"567 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"41 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"6 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"493 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"61", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"24 : 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"260 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"48 : 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"396 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"267 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"20 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"421 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"168 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"128 : 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"67 : 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"170 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"318 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"42", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"383 : 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"63", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"55 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"231 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"489 : 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"458 : 64 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"123 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"220 : 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"447 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"33", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"500 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"310 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"50", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"220 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"493 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"195 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"40 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"143 : 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"438 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"35 : 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"610 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"71", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"145 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"193 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"341 : 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"58 : 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"58", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"302 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"135 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"15 : 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"225 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"114 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"195 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"143 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"10 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"126 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"320 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"36", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"678 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"330 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"185 : 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"407 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"84 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"115 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"241 : 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"323 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"522 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"34 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"168 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"512 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"534 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"630 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"420 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"334 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"161 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"9 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"6 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"69 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"643 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"666 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"58", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"84 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"361 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"429 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"170 : 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"110 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"7 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"13 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"189 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"520 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"481 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"423 : 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"52", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"214 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"39 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"296 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"376 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"37 : 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"199 : 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"133 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"42 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"108 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"118 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"381 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"30 : 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"41 : 53 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"278 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"179 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"556 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"14 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"354 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"110 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"337 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"57", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"109 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"196 : 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"97 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"714 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"389 : 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"69", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"16 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"16", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"113 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"202 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"441 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"324 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"299 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"292 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"101 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"269 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"29", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"581 : 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"56", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"180 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"54", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"278 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"363 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"5 : 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"460 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"68 : 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"137 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"307 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"310 : 60 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"214 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"37", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"83 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"242 : 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"620 : 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"97 : 25 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"58 : 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"58", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"106 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"20 : 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"565 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"179 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"319 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"43", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"98 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"221 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"453 : 59 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"118 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"447 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"322 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"206 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"33 : 78 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"33", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"107 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"311 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"125 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"123 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"53", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"264 : 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"580 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"69", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"24 : 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"194 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"125 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"518 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"62", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"342 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"351 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"197 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"47 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"479 : 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"47", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"27 : 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"4 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"80 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"26 : 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"56 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"161 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"280 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"102 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"325 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"486 : 50 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"36", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"185 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"558 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"432 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"160 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"83 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"623 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"29", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"299 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"33", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"24 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"315 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"371 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"11 : 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"2 : 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"269 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"537 : 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"61", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"379 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"36", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"91 : 33 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"19 : 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"123 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"139 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"30 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"272 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"133 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"197 : 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"267 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"8 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"634 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"340 : 75 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"40 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"135 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"66", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"110 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"115 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"212 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"270 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"263 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"152 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"170 : 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"74 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"128 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"1 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"603 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"19 : 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"390 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"418 : 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"245 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"579 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"51", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"447 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"210 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"260 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"59", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"13 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"450 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"70", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"90 : 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"125 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"59", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"289 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"44", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"401 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"56", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"100 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"45", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"189 : 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"482 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"42", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"25 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"491 : 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"161 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"192 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"367 : 62 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"57", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"248 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"52 : 29 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"327 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"163 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"13 : 31 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"222 : 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"48", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"324 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"9 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"167 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"11", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"366 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"219 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"49 : 77 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"7 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"7", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"5 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"137 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"66", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"49 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"643 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"519 : 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"55", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"433 : 57 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"701 : 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"69", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"329 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"25", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"122 : 73 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"49", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"399 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"29", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"392 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"252 : 79 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"435 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"178 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"68 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"47 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"152 : 54 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"44", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"2 : 67 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"23 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"10 : 16 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"69 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"23", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"342 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"66", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"491 : 70 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"285 : 43 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"22 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"466 : 66 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"35 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"116 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"354 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"70", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"13 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"389 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"20", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"132 : 20 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"6 : 65 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"40 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"27 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"222 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"60 : 69 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"60", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"136 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"134 : 30 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"234 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"40 : 80 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"40", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"2 : 36 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"216 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"418 : 44 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"9 : 61 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"9", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"236 : 74 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"38 : 45 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"38", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"17 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"94 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"46", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"82 : 56 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"249 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"425 : 51 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"17", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"218 : 24 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"182 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"34", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"1 : 21 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"1", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"254 : 58 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"282 : 32 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"18 : 38 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"18", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"3 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"37 : 22 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"10 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"10", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"702 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"54", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"5 : 28 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"5", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"303 : 72 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"15", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"600 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"32", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"242 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"275 : 40 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"35", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"69 : 55 = ?","answers":[{"value":"1", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"86 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"2", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"26 : 76 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"31 : 35 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"558 : 68 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"19 : 49 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"19", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"335 : 42 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"41", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"130 : 39 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"6 : 37 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"6", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"147 : 15 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"123 : 34 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"21", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"429 : 71 = ?","answers":[{"value":"6", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"3", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"291 : 52 = ?","answers":[{"value":"5", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"31", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"534 : 63 = ?","answers":[{"value":"8", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"30", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"344 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"132 : 27 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"24", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"27 : 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"59 : 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"2", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"28 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"28", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"76 : 18 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"4", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"368 : 47 = ?","answers":[{"value":"7", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"39", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"27 : 41 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"27", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"161 : 17 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"8", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"22 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"22", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"81 : 23 = ?","answers":[{"value":"3", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"13 : 46 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"13", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"248 : 26 = ?","answers":[{"value":"9", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"14", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"218 : 48 = ?","answers":[{"value":"4", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"26", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
{"question":"12 : 19 = ?","answers":[{"value":"0", "hint":"Частное?"},{"value":"12", "hint":"Остаток?"}]}
